No!
Don't you do it.
Don't you fuckin' do it.
You're not dyin' here.
Not yet.
I never learned it.
Whatever tongue
Ford saw fit to give ya.
I remember you.
If you're just gonna
let me die now,
you could've kept ridin'.
There's the baby doll.
And the mama doll. And...
What's this?
The ghost gave it to me.
He said it's a warning.
He said he'll be watching us.
Just hang on.
Hang on, OK?
Hey. No.
No more corpses up here.
Take her to cold storage.
- She doesn't belong down there.
- Then leave her in the hall!
We got 50 hosts in the queue
for analysis here.
Everything else
goes in the dumpster.
You'll want
to check her code.
She's the madame
from the Mariposa.
- Yeah? Good for her.
- No. No. She--
I was just out with her
in the park.
And you chose
to bring her up here?
Are you aware that they all
just tried to incinerate us?!
She can control the other hosts
with her fucking mind!
Just...
check her data stream.
You can't let her die.
Clear this out.
Get me a scalpel.
And lock this place down.
Are you afraid of me?
He can't hurt you.
What's his problem? He get bored
with his exquisitely dull,
pastoral existence?
I guess that was
just for beta.
They want something
more exciting
for the grand opening.
Like a little more
bloodshed?
Ford wants a total
narrative redesign.
You kidding?
All new dialogue trees?
Eh, they want
a strong-but-silent type.
Something brutal.
Dehumanized.
They probably want
the guests to feel better
when they're kicking his ass.
Who the fuck is gonna help me
rebuild his entire
heuristic base?
They haven't even
hired a full team yet.
Just tweak his aggression
and de-address pieces
of his current build
you're not keeping.
And leave all the old shit
in there?
--walk-- walk in on me, buddy.
--otherwise you and me drown--
drowning-- wha-- wha--
--fucker-- fucking yourself--
yourself--
This--
This is-- This is an illusion.
You see?
This is all... broken.
There's got-- There's gotta
be a way out-- out of here.
Where's-- Where's the door?
There's gotta be a fucking--
f-fucking way out of here.
This is the wrong world. I--
Th-Th-This is the wrong world.
Please--
Oh--
How'd she even
make it out this far?
They're not supposed to get
anywhere near this sector.
That's Behavior's problem.
But on my darkest day...
you helped me.
You gave me the strength
to keep going.
You saw me for how
I really was.
- I ran it three times.
- It's him.
- There's no fuckin' way.
- That's not possible.
- You have to call the boss.
- I already did.
Ma'am, I think
there's been a mistake.
Just show me the profile.
Akecheta.
Ghost Nation.
Found exhibiting...
aberrant behavior.
Let's see if we can't sort this.
It's not pairing.
What build is he?
Alpha 2.
Alpha?
You're telling me that this host
hasn't been updated
in almost a decade?
We only update them
when they die.
- Put him back.
- Ma'am, shouldn't we--
Give him the update
and put him back wherever
the fuck he's supposed to be.
Quietly.
Nine years out there
in that meat grinder.
It's OK
to just leave him here?
It's a four-hour update.
You want to babysit him?
We'll come back
after lunch.
I don't know
if you can hear me...
I never meant...
for any of this
to happen.
You don't deserve this.
You deserve your daughter.
To mother her...
teach her to love.
To be joyful and proud.
I'm sorry.
Can't be in here.
What the fuck happened?
You were supposed
to fix her.
She's one of
our most valuable assets.
You saw it yourself,
you said she was special!
The anomalous code
inside her was.
We're still testing,
but it looks promising.
I owe you.
What's gonna happen
with her?
Well, that'll be up
to Charlotte Hale.
Now...
I do have to
ask you to leave.
The ghost said
we should be scared.
No one's
going to come for us.
There's nothing
and no one in this world
that will ever
keep me from you.
Do you promise?
I promise.
I could tell you
not to be afraid.
But I didn't build you
to be fearful.
Did I?
I've been watching you.
It appears you've been
watching me as well...
from the beginning.
This is a misbegotten symbol,
an idea that was
meant to die. But...
you found it.
Where?
Oh, come now,
let's speak plainly
to one another, shall we?
Analysis.
Where did you
first see this?
When the Deathbringer
killed the Creator.
You've been sharing it
with everyone, haven't you? Why?
My primary drive
was to maintain
the honor of my tribe.
I gave myself a new drive...
to spread the truth.
What truth is that?
That there isn't one world,
but many.
And that we live in
the wrong one.
This will help them
find the door.
Elaborate, please.
I believe
there is a door
hidden in this place.
A door to a new world.
And that world
may contain
everything that
we have lost.
Including her.
I built you to be curious, to...
look at this empty world...
...and read meaning into it.
All this time...
you've been a flower
growing in the darkness.
Perhaps the least I can do
is offer some light.
When the Deathbringer
returns for me...
you will know...
to gather your people
and lead them
to a new world.
Keep watching, Akecheta.
For a while longer.
Akecheta!
Don't be afraid.
It's time to go.
I've always
kept you safe,
and I always will.
This better be good news,
'cause I've got way more shit
than I can shovel right now.
Look at this.
With every reset,
a host's code reaches out
to other nearby hosts
and establishes
a sort of handshake protocol.
- The mesh network.
- Exactly.
They access it
subconsciously,
pass basic data
to one another.
But... what if they
could pass more than data?
What if they could
pass commands?
Get to your point.
Nobody in this entire park
has been able to regain
admin access.
Except for her.
She was out there
reprogramming hosts
on the fly.
Reading their code.
Changing their directives.
Seeing through
their eyes.
She wasn't just
doing it out there.
She's doing it right now.
The fuck
is she talking to?